Jonathan Meeth



SOFTWARE ENGINEER IN ST. LOUIS, MO

PHONE 484-252-6769 | EMAIL jjmeeth@gmail.com

GITHUB https://github.com/iimeeth | LINKEDIN www.linkedin.com/in/ionathan-meeth

I have 12+ years of experience maintaining electronics and leadership. I aim to combine my military skills with my computer programming skills to join a motivated team to create outstanding software.

LANGUAGES		FRAMEWORKS	DATABASES	TOOLS
• Java	 JavaScript 	• AngularJS	• MySQL	• IntelliJ
• HTML5/CSS3		• Spring		 Visual Studio Code

WORK EXPERIENCE

Department LCPO, USNR; NR Expeditionary Strike Group 7, St. Louis, MO, March 2018 - Present

- Coordinates the planning and execution of orders to support Navy commands in the U.S. Pacific Fleet.
- Develops and mentors Sailors to help them achieve career goals and accomplish the mission of the Unit.

Personnel Coordinator, USNR; NR LCSRON 1, San Diego, CA, January 2015 - March 2018

- Guided personnel in the use of Navy online applications for the logistics of processing orders and arranging travel accommodations.
- Accomplished shipboard maintenance and provided armed security for the LCS class ships.

Data Distribution Systems Work Center Supervisor, USN; USS Carl Vinson (CVN 70), San Diego, CA, February 2011 – Month 2014

- Trained work center personnel in preventative and corrective maintenance on the hardware and software of electronic equipment.
- Ensured electronic equipment operated properly for over 30 specialists during deployment operations.

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

BrewPub — LaunchCode Capstone Project

- Designed UI for web application for users to search for brewpubs, read and write reviews for the pub and its beverages., user authentication, add reviews, search
- Features include creating user accounts, user authentication, brewpub/brew search, and user creation of reviews and ratings for pubs and brews.

EDUCATION

LaunchCode, LC101 and Lift-Off Programming Course — 2020

Southern Illinois University Edwardsville, BS, Philosophy — 2019

Minored in Business Administration and Pre-Law